

Profile

I am a Frontend developer with more than 1 year of development experience. I have experience with various Frontend development technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Redux, Ant Design, Bootstrap and have completed more than 10 pet-projects. I am a quick learner and able to quickly adapt to new projects and technologies.

Employment History

Passing practice at Administrative services center, Klevan

May, 2022 — July, 2022

I performed the duties of a Frontend developer such as:

- Developed a website for Administrative services center by using HTML, CSS, JavaScript and Bootstrap.
- Transferred the website to the content management system WordPress.
- Using WordPress, added some Backend functionality (electronic queue and Newsline)

Internship at RenomeSmart, Rivne

December, 2021 — June, 2022

RenomeLab is a student program of RenomeSmart. The purpose of the program is to create social projects to improve the city. I was a member of the Lab_1 team and performed the role of a software engineer:

- Designed parking system.
- Created a layout of a parking application in Figma.
- Tested user interface.
- Presented the project to local authorities.

Education

Bachelor, National university of life and environmental sciences of Ukraine, Kyiv

September 2022 — Present

Specialty 121 "Software Engineering"

Junior specialist, Rivne professional college of national university of life and environmental sciences of Ukraine, Rivne

September 2018 — June 2022

Specialty 121 "Software Engineering"

Courses

React and Redux, YouTube

November 2022 — Present

JavaScript Advanced, ITVDN

August 2022 — August 2022

JavaScript Starter, ITVDN

April 2022 — May 2022

English, Duolingo

April 2022 — Present

HTML & CSS Essential, ITVDN

July 2022 — August 2022

IT Essential, Cisco Academy

October 2021 — November 2021

Details

Kyiv

Ukraine

+380974473766

svyryd2012@gmail.com

Links

Github

Portfolio

LinkedIn

CodeWars

Skills

HTML

CSS

Experienced

Experienced

JavaScript

React

Experienced

Skillful

Bootstrap

Redux

Skillful

Skillful

Git

Ant Design Experienced

Basic

SQL

Rest API

Basic

Basic

Languages

Ukrainian: Native

English: B1